Archival Collective Bargaining Agreements File 6030
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Archival Collective Bargaining Agreements File
1997-2013
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives
6030
257.5 cubic feet
256 linear ft.
Records.
This is a collection of papers dealing with various types of collective bargaining agreements.
5772839
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, February 10, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 17, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780/075: ILGWU Collective Bargaining Agreements 5780/202: ILGWU Operations Department Collective Bargaining Agreements 6000/008: UNITE Operations Department Collective Bargaining Agreements 6055: UTU Additional Collective Bargaining Agreements 6124: Collective Bargaining Agreements for New York State Employees 6178: BLS/OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements 6287: Martin Scheinman Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements 6297: Peter A. Gold Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements 6337: Seyfarth Shaw Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements
Collective labor agreements -- New York (State); Arbitration, Industrial -- New York (State)
5772839
- American Federation of Labor Agreements 1946-1949 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- AFL. Aluminum Trades Council, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- AFL- Building Trades Dept. 1919-1949 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- AFL- Building Trades Dept. 1950-1961 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- AFL- Federal Labor Union, 1950-1959 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- AFL- Federal Labor Union 1940-1945 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- AFL. Federal Labor Union 22619, 1950-1959 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- AFL. Federal Labor Union No. 22703, 1952-1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- AFL- Federal Labor Union, 1942-1949 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Federal Labor Union Lisk-Savory Corporation 101438, 1956-1964 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- AFL- Federal Labor Unions Agreements, 1950-1954 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Hotel Trades Council, 1951-1966 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- NY Hotel Trades Council w/ Hotel Association of NY, 1939-1942 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- AFL- Metal Trades Dept., 1950-1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- AFL- Metal Trades Dept. 1950-1977 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Railway Labor: Organizations, 1919-1949 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO Allied Trades Council, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO Buffalo Hospital Council, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO Farm Workers, United Agreements, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- 55-37 Federal Labor Unions Agreements, 1954-1957 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Federal Labor AFL-CIO Unions 58-59, 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- AFL- Federal Labor Unions 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- AFL- Federal Labor Union 1965-1969 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO Hotel Trades Council, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- CIO- Local Industrial Unions Agreements 1940-1949 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- CIO- Local Industrial Unions 1950-1959 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO Metal Trades Council, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO Tennessee Valley Trades and Labor Council, 1951-1964 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO University of Chicago Council, 1957-1959 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Actor's Equity 1945-1949 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Actor's Equity 1950-1954 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Actor's Equity 1955-1959 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Actor's Equity 1960-1966 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Actor's Equity Association w/ Employees 1986-1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Am. Guild of Musical Artists 45-66, 1945-1966 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Screen Actors Before 1940 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Actors and Artistes Screen Actors Guild, 1945-1949 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Actors and Artists - Screen Actors Guild '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Actors and Artists - Screen Actors '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Actors and Actors - Screen Actors Guild '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Actors and Artists of Screen Actors Guild, 1963-1979 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Actors and Artists Assoc. Screen Extras Guild '65, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Actors and Artists Assoc. Screen Extras Guild 1963- (Box 4, Folder 10)
- AFTRA 1940-1944 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- AFTRA 1945-1949 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Actors and Artists AFTRA '50-'55, 1950-1955 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Actors and Artists of America, Associated AFTRA '56-'59, 1956-1959 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Actors and Artists - Television and Radio Artists '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Actors and Artists AFTRA 65-69, 1965-1969 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- AFTRA 1970-75, 1970-1975 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Actors and Artists Variety Artists 1953- (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Air Line Dispatchers 1940-1949 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Air Line Dispatchers 1950-1954 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Air Line Dispatchers Association 1955-1959 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Airline Dispatchers 1960-1965 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Air Line Employees Association. Intl. 1960-1967 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Airline Dispatchers 1970-75, 1970-1975 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Air Line Flight Agents, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Airline Mechanics Association, International Agreements, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Airline Meteorologists Assoc. 1947, 1947-1948 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Air Line Pilots Assn. 1939-1944 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Air Line Pilots Assn. 1939-1944 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Air Line Pilot Association, Intl. Agreements 45-49, 1945-1949 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Air Carrier Communication Operators Assn, Intl. Agreements, 1945-1951 (Box 5.1, Folder 1)
- Air Carrier Mechanics, 1953 (Box 5.1, Folder 2)
- National Airlines, Inc., 1958-1959 (Box 5.1, Folder 3)
- Airline Agents 1960-1964 (Box 5.1, Folder 4)
- Airlines Communications Employees Ass'n 1950-1954 (Box 5.1, Folder 5)
- Airlines Communications Employees Association Unaffiliated, 1956-1988 (Box 5.1, Folder 6)
- Delta Airlines Agreements (Air Line Pilots Association), 1990-2007 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- The Airline Pilots Association, International, 1981-1985 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- The Airline Pilots Association, International Agreements, 1944-1967 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Air Line Pilots Association 60-64, 1960-1964 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Air Line Pilots Association Agreements, 1953-1963 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Air Line Pilots Association, 1950-1954 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Air Line Pilots 1955-1959 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Airline Stewards and Stewardesses Ass'n., Int' Agreements, 1965-1974 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Air Line Pilots 65-69, 1965-1971 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Airline Pilots 1970 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Air Line Pilots Association, 1979-1985 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Air Lines Stewards 1950-1954 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Air Line Stewards and Stewarderers, 1955-1959 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Air Line Stewards and Stewardesses Assoc. 1960-1965 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Air Navigators, Assn. of, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Air Traffic Controllers Assoc, Nat'l., 1993 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Alaska Public Employee's Association, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Allied and Technical Workers of U.S. and Canada Agreements, 1970-1972 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Allied Industrial Workers, 1958-1962 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Aluminum Brick and Glass Workers, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Aluminum Workers 1935-1949 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Aluminum Workers Int'l Union 1950-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Aluminum Workers '65-'69, 1965-1969 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Aluminum Workers '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Aluminum Workers '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1983-1986 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- American Association of University Professors, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- FAECT Internat'l Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians, CIO, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Asbestos Workers 1950-54, 1950-1954 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Asbestos Workers 1955-1959 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Asbestos Workers 1960-1964 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Asbestos Workers 1965-1969 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Associated Unions of America Agreements 1944-1950 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Automobile - waw-CIO, 1937-1950 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Automobile Workers A,F.L. 1940-1944 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- UAW -1945-1949 A-B (Box 9, Folder 2)
- UAW-CIO Local 125, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- UAW - 1945-1949 C-D (Box 9, Folder 4)
- UAW - Chrysler - 1945-1949 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- UAW - 1945-1949 E-J (Box 9, Folder 6)
- UAW General Motors- 1945-1949 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- UAW Ford -1945-1949 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- UAW-1945-1949 - K-M (Box 9, Folder 9)
- UAW- 1945-1949 - N-S (Box 9, Folder 10)
- UAW -1945-1949 - T-Z (Box 9, Folder 11)
- UAW- 1950-1954 -A-B (Box 10, Folder 1)
- UAW 1950-1954 -C (Box 10, Folder 2)
- UAW- 1950-1954 -G-H (Box 10, Folder 3)
- UAW - 1950-1954 -D-F (Box 10, Folder 4)
- UAW -1950-1954 -I-L (Box 10, Folder 5)
- UAW -1950-1954 - M-O (Box 10, Folder 6)
- UAW -1950-1954- P-S (Box 10, Folder 7)
- UAW -1950-1954 T-Z (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Bell Aircraft Corporation Union Contracts for 1954 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Union Agreements, 1950-1959 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- UAW - 1955-1959- A (Box 11, Folder 4)
- UAW-1955-1959 -B (Box 11, Folder 5)
- United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1959-1979 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Settlement Agreement, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- UAW - 1955-1959 -C (Box 12, Folder 2)
- UAW - 1955-1959 -D-E (Box 12, Folder 3)
- UAW - 1955-1959 -F (Box 12, Folder 4)
- UAW - 1955-1959 -G (Box 12, Folder 5)
- UAW- 1955-1959 -H-L (Box 13, Folder 1)
- UAW- 1955-1959- M (Box 13, Folder 2)
- UAW- 1955-1959 - N-S (Box 13, Folder 3)
- UAW -1955-1959 -T-Y (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Agreements, 1959-1962 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- UAW - 1960-1964 - A-B (Box 14, Folder 1)
- UAW - 1960-1964 - C-E (Box 14, Folder 2)
- UAW 1960-1964 - F (Box 15, Folder 1)
- UAW - 1960-1964 - G (Box 15, Folder 2)
- UAW -1960-1964 - H-L (Box 16, Folder 1)
- UAW - 1960-1964 - M-N (Box 16, Folder 2)
- UAW - 1960-1964 - O-Z (Box 16, Folder 3)
- UAW - 1965-1969 - A (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Labor Agreements AFL-CIO, 1965-2004 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- UAW -1965-1969 -B (Box 17, Folder 3)
- UAW- 1965-1969 - C (Box 17, Folder 4)
- UAW - 1965-1969 - D-E (Box 17, Folder 5)
- UAW - 1965-1969 -F (Box 17, Folder 6)
- UAW - 1965-1969 - G (Box 17, Folder 7)
- UAW - 1965-1969 - H-J (Box 17, Folder 8)
- UAW- 1965-1969 -K-L (Box 17, Folder 9)
- UAW - 1965-1969 -M (Box 17, Folder 10)
- UAW -1965-1969 - N-O (Box 17, Folder 11)
- UAW - 1965-1969 -P (Box 17, Folder 12)
- UAW- 1965-1969 -Q-R (Box 17, Folder 13)
- UAW - 1965-1969 - S (Box 17, Folder 14)
- UAW - 1965-1969 - T (Box 17, Folder 15)
- UAW - 1965-1969 - U-V (Box 17, Folder 16)
- UAW - 1965-1969 - W-Z (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Automotive and Aircraft Workers Union, 1962-1965 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- A-K, 1968-1982 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- UAW Agreements, 1968-1983 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- AMC, 1970-1988 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Chrysler, 1973-1996 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Chrysler, 1993-1999 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Cornell, 1985-2001 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Ford, 1970-2003 (Box 19A, Folder 1)
- Ford, 1970-2003 (Box 19B, Folder 1)
- General Motors, 1970-1981 (Box 19A, Folder 2)
- GM, 1982-1996 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Int'l Harvester, 1973-2003 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Maytag, 1971-1995 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Mazda, 1991-1994 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- McDonnell Douglas, 1971-1991 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- New United Motor Manufacturing, Inc., 1988-1998 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Saturn, 1994-1996 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Automotive Workers Ind., 1945 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Bakery and Confectionary Workers, 1940-1944 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Bakery and Confectionary Workers' International Union of America Agreements 1945-1949 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Bakery, Int'l., 1950-1954 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Bakery and Confectionary Workers' Int'l. Union of America 1955-1959 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Bakery and Confectionary Workers, Ind. Master Contract, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Bakery and Confectionary Workers, 1957-1959 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Bakery and Confectionery Workers 2, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Bakery and Confectionary, American Drake Bakeries Inc., 1963 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Bakery and Confectionery Workers Agreements, 1960-1963 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Bakery and Confectionary Workers Union, 1960-1962 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Bakery Workers '65-'69, 1965-1969 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Bakery and Confectionery Workers' Int'l., 1960-1964 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Barbers and Beauty Culturists Union of America Agreements '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Barbers and Beauty Culturists Union of America Agreements '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Barbers and Beauty Culturists 1955-1959 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Barbers, Hairdressers, Cosmetologists and Properties '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Barbers, H.C.P. '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Barbers, Hairdressers, Cosmetologists, - Proprietors - 1960-1964 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Barbers Terminal Barber Shops, Inc., 1961-1963 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Barbers International Union of America, Journeymen - 1955-1959 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Barbers International Union of America, Journeymen - 1960-1964 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Baseball, 1973-1990 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Bills Posters and Distributors Union '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Bill Posters - 1960-1964 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Blacksmiths '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Boilermakers, Ironship Builders, Helpers of Amer. Int'l Bro, of Agreements '40-'49, 1940-1949 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Boilermakers '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Boilermakers '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Boiler Makers, Iron Ship Builders and Helpers of America, Int'l. Bro. '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers, and Helpers, 1965-1969 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Bookbinders '40-'44, 1940-1944 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Bookbinders, International Brotherhood of Agreements '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Bookbinders '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Bookbinders '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Bookbinders Int'l Brotherhood '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Bookbinders, International Brotherhood of - 1965-1969 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Bookbinders, International, Brotherhood of. 1969- (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Brewery, Flour and Cereal, Soft Drink and Distill. Wkrs. Of Amer. Int'l Union Unit. Agreements '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Bookbinders, Int'l Brotherhood Agreements 1971, 1949-1971 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Brewery '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Brewery '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Brewery Workers - 1960-1964 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Brewery Workers 1965-1969 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Standard Brands General Agreement, 1918-1945 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Birmingham, Alabama - Jackson, California, 1937-1945 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Los Angeles, Calif., 1937-1945 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Los Angeles, Calif., 1913-1945 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Oakland, California - San Diego, California, 1939-1945 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- San Francisco, Calif., 1939-1945 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- San Francisco, Calif., 1918-1945 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- San Jose, California - Boulder, Colorado, 1935-1938 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Denver, Colorado Brewery and Distr., 1909-1945 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Golden, Colorado - Pueblo, Colorado, 1909-1945 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Trinidad, Colorado, 1913-1945 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- State of Connecticut Bridgeport, Connecticut - Danbury, Connecticut, 1909-1945 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Hartford, Connecticut Meriden, Connecticut, 1902-1945 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- New Haven, Connecticut, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Waterbury, Connecticut - Wilmington, Delaware, 1951-1978 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Washington, D.C., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Jacksonville, Florida, 1914-1945 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Miami, Florida - West Palm Beach, Florida, 1935-1945 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Atlanta, Georgia - Savannah, Georgia, 1936-1945 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Boise, Idaho - Wallace, Idaho, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Alton, Illinois - Aurora, Illinois, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Belleville, Illinois - Cairo, Illinois, 1907-1945 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Chicago, Illinois Brewery 1925-45, 1925-1945 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Chicago, Illinois Brewery 1908-1925 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Chicago, Illinois Bottle Drivers, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Chicago, Illinois Keg Drivers (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Chicago, Illinois - Chicago Heights, Illinois (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Chicago, Illinois Malt, 1909-1945 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Chrystal Lake, Illinois - Galena, Illinois, 1940-1945 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Highland, Illinois - Kankakee, Illinois, 1911-1945 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- McHenry, Illinois - Ottawa, Illinois, 1945 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Pekin, Illinois - Peoria, Illinois, 1912-1928 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Peru, Illinois - Rock Island, Illinois (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Rockford, Illinois - Waukegan, Illinois, 1914-1949 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Anderson, Indiana, 1910-1941 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Evansville, Indiana Brewery (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Evansville. Indiana - Fort Wayne, Indiana (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Indianapolis, Indiana Brewery and Distr., 1957 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Indianapolis, Indiana Soft Drink, 1949-1950 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Lafayette, Indiana - Logansport, Indiana, 1918-1948 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Marion, Indiana - South Bend, Indiana (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Summitville, Indiana - Vincennes, Indiana, 1912-1942 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Cedar Rapids, Iowa - Davenport, Iowa, 1910-1945 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Des Moines, Iowa - Waverly, Iowa, 1911-1957 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Ashland, Kentucky - Lexington, Kentucky, 1918-1948 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Louisville, Kentucky - Paducah, Kentucky, 1912-1949 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Gretna, Louisiana - New Orleans, Louisiana, 1917-1947 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Baltimore, Maryland Brewery, 1933 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Baltimore, Maryland Distributor, 1947-1949 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Baltimore, Maryland Yeast, 1918-1946 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Baltimore, Maryland Soft Drink and Syrup, 1931-1945 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Cumberland, Maryland - Hagerstown, Maryland, 1909-1936 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- State of Massachusetts - Boston, Massachusetts, 1920-1946 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Chicopee, Massachusetts - Lawrence, Massachusetts, 1922-1948 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Lowell, Massachusetts - Worcester, Massachusetts, 1904-1949 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Alpena, Michigan - Bay City, Michigan, 1910-1948 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Detroit, Michigan Brewery, 1935-1943 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Detroit, Michigan Brewery 1943-50, 1943-1950 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Detroit, Michigan Distributor 1949-50, 1949-1950 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Detroit, Michigan Distributor, 1946 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Detroit, Michigan Malt, Grain and Wine, 1908-1935 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Detroit, Michigan Distributor 1946-50, 1946-1950 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Escanaba, Michigan - Frankenburgh, Michigan (Also Flint and Saginaw), 1934-1945 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Grand Rapids, Michigan - Houghton, Michigan, 1915-1919 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Ionia, Michigan - Monroe, Michigan, 1935-1945 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Mt. Clemens - Ypsilanti, Michigan, 1915-1945 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- State of Minnesota Cannon Falls, Minnesota Cold Spring, Minnesota Duluth, Minnesota (Also Superior, Wisc.), 1926-1948 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- East Grand Forks, Minnesota - Mankato, Minnesota, 1910-1945 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Minneapolis-St. Paul, Minnesota, 1935-1945 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Minneapolis-St. Paul, Minnesota Soft Drink, 1942 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Minneapolis, Minn. Malt and Grain, 1911-1928 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Montgomery, Minnesota, 1937-1939 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- New Ulm, Minnesota - St. Cloud, Minnesota, 1915-1945 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- St. Paul Minn. (See Minneapolis), 1927-1945 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- St. Peter, Minnesota - Winona, Minnesota, 1913-1943 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Cape Girardeau, Missouri - Joplin, Missouri, 1918-1945 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Kansas City, Missouri - Brewery and Distr., 1931-1943 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Kansas City, Missouri Soft Drink Syrup and Misc., 1917-1942 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- St. Joseph, Missouri - Brewery and Distr., 1911-1950 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- St. Joseph, Missouri Soft Drink Vinegar, 1920-1947 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- St. Louis, Missouri - Brewery, 1944 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- St. Louis, Missouri Brewery 1944-1950 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- St. Louis, Missouri Soft Drink Yeast Corn and Syrup, 1924-1940 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- St. Louis, Missouri Brewery Proposals, 1913-1950 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- St. Louis, Missouri Amalgamation of #303 With #187, 1919 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- St. Louis, Missouri Out of Work Decision 1921-1922 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- St. Louis, Missouri Brewery Decisions 1918-1919 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- St. Louis, Missouri Agreements with Other Trades, 1914-1915 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- St. Louis, Missouri 1921 Situation (Box 37, Folder 9)
- St. Louis, Missouri Freight Handlers Decision, 1918-1919 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Anaconda, Montana - Butte, Montana (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Dillon, Montana - Red Lodge, Montana, 1920-1950 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Crete, Nebraska - Omaha, Nebraska, 1911-1950 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Carson City-Reno, Nevada Ely, Nevada, 1911-1947 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Manchester, New Hampshire - Portsmouth, New Hampshire, 1916-1948 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Asbury Park, New Jersey - Jersey City, New Jersey, 1936-1945 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Newark, New Jersey Brewery 1944-50, 1944-1950 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Newark, New Jersey Brewery, 1936-1944 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Newark, New Jersey, 1917-1950 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Orange, New Jersey - Perth Amboy, New Jersey, 1933-1945 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Trenton, New Jersey - Union City, New Jersey, 1923-1945 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Albuquerque, New Mexico, 1916-1924 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Akron, New York - Albany, New York (Also Troy) (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Amsterdam, New York - Bridgewater, New York, 1920-1939 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Buffalo, New York Brewery and Distr. 1945-50, 1945-1950 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Buffalo, New York Brewery and Distr., 1916-1945 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- New York and Brooklyn, New York Brewery, 1930-1945 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Buffalo, New York Feed and Syrup, 1923-1950 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Buffalo, New York Malt, 1921-1929 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Buffalo, New York Soft Drink, 1933-1949 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Candaigua, New York - Hornell, New York (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Hudson, New York - Newburgh, New York, 1917-1948 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- New York, N.Y., 1938-1945 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- New York, N.Y., 1937-1941 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- New York, N.Y., 1942 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- New York, N.Y., 1921-1941 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- New York, N.Y. (Box 41, Folder 5)
- New York, N.Y., 1946-1950 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- New York, N.Y., 1945-1950 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Niagara Falls, New York, 1916-1929 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Norwich, New York - Peekskill, New York (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Port Jervis, New York - Poughkeepsie, New York, 1913-1948 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Rochester, New York, 1918-1946 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Schenectady, New York, 1914-1950 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Sodus Point, New York, 1918-1950 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Syracuse, New York, 1910-1949 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Tonawanda, New York, 1916-1945 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Troy, New York, 1907-1922 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Utica, New York, 1937 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Watkins Glen, New York Watertown, (Also Lowville), 1939-1949 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Charlotte, North Carolina - Winston-Salem North Carolina, 1942-1947 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Akron, Ohio - Bellaire, Ohio, 1949-1950 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Canton, Ohio - Chillicothe, Ohio, 1915-1942 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Cincinnati, Ohio, 1919-1951 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Cleveland, Ohio Bry and Distr. (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Cleveland, Ohio Soft Drink, 1917-1935 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Cleveland, Ohio 1935 Strike (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Columbus, Ohio, 1915-1942 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Dayton, Ohio - Bry and Distr., 1915-1942 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Dayton, Ohio Soft Drink, 1925-1948 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Defiance, Ohio - Glouster, Ohio, 1918-1950 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Hamilton, Ohio - Lima, Ohio, 1947-1950 (Box 45, Folder 3)